<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Finger-Licken Good</string>


    <string name="c1">•	1 1/2 lbs liempo</string>
    <string name="c2">•	1 piece Knorr Pork Cube</string>
    <string name="c3">•	1 piece purple yam ube, cubed</string>
    <string name="c4">•	1 1/2 cups kalabasa cubed</string>
    <string name="c5">•	12 pieces sitaw sliced in 2 inch pieces</string>
    <string name="c6">•	10 pieces okra</string>
    <string name="c7">•	1 pieces talong sliced</string>
    <string name="c8">•	1 piece ampalaya sliced</string>
    <string name="c9">•	1 piece tomato cubed</string>
    <string name="c10">• 1 piece onion chopped</string>
    <string name="c11">• 3 thumbs ginger crushed</string>
    <string name="c12">• 4 cloves garlic chopped</string>
    <string name="c13">• 3 tablespoons bagoong alamang</string>
    <string name="c14">• 5 cups water for boiling</string>
    <string name="c15">•	3 tablespoons cooking oil</string>
    <string name="c16">•	Ground black pepper to taste</string>

    <string name="c17">
 •	1 lb. pig ears \n
•	1 1/2 lb pork belly\n
•	1 piece onion minced\n
•	3 tablespoons soy sauce \n
•	1/4 teaspoon ground black pepper \n
•	1 knob ginger minced (optional)  \n
•	3 tablespoons chili flakes \n
•	1/2 teaspoon garlic powder \n
•	1 piece lemon or 3 to 5 pieces calamansi \n
•	½ cup butter or margarine \n
•	¼ lb chicken liver \n
•	6 cups water \n
•	3 tablespoons mayonnaise \n
•	1/2 teaspoon salt \n
•	1 piece egg (optional) \n
</string>

    <string name="c18">
1.	Pour the water in a pan and bring to a boil Add salt and pepper. \n\n
2.	Put-in the pig’s ears and pork belly then simmer for 40 minutes to 1 hour (or until tender).\n\n
3.	Remove the boiled ingredients from the pot then drain excess water\n\n
4.	Grill the boiled pig ears and pork belly until done\n\n
5.	Chop the pig ears and pork belly into fine pieces\n\n
6.	In a wide pan, melt the butter or margarine. Add the onions. Cook until onions are soft.\n\n
7.	Put-in the ginger and cook for 2 minutes\n\n
8.	Add the chicken liver. Crush the chicken liver while cooking it in the pan.\n\n
9.	Add the chopped pig ears and pork belly. Cook for 10 to 12 minutes\n\n
10.	Put-in the soy sauce, garlic powder, and chili. Mix well\n\n
11.	Add salt and pepper to taste\n\n
12.	Put-in the mayonnaise and mix with the other ingredients\n\n
13.	Transfer to a serving plate. Top with chopped green onions and raw egg.\n\n
14.	Serve hot. Share and Enjoy (add the lemon or calamansi before eating)

    </string>

    <string name="c19">
•	1 1/2 lbs. pork belly cubed\n
•	1 cup pineapple juice\n
•	10 ounces extra firm tofu cubed\n
•	1/4 cup soy sauce\n
•	2 tablespoons white vinegar\n
•	6 tablespoons brown sugar\n
•	4 tablespoons salted black beans\n
•	1 piece onion chopped\n
•	6 cloves garlic crushed and chopped\n
•	1 piece star anise\n
•	1 cup water\n
•	1/4 teaspoon ground black pepper\n
•	1 1/2 cups cooking oil\n
    </string>

    <string name="c20">
1.	Heat cooking oil in a wok or cooking pot. Add tofu. Deep fry until outer part turns golden brown and crisp. Remove from the wok. Set aside.\n\n
2.	Transfer 3 tablespoons cooking oil used to fry tofu on a clean pan. Heat and saute garlic until it starts to brown. Add onion. Continue sauteing until the later softens.\n\n
3.	Add pork. Cook until the outer part turns light brown.\n\n
4.	Pour soy sauce. Continue sauteing until liquid reduces to half.\n\n
5.	Add pineapple juice and vinegar. Cover and let boil.\n\n
6.	Stir and then add salted black beans. Cover once more. Continue cooking between low to medium heat for 35 minutes.\n\n
7.	Add water and brown sugar. Cook on a covered pan until pork gets very tender. Note: I usually cook it for 40 minutes in low heat.\n\n
8.	Add star anise. Cook for 5 minutes. Remove star anise from the wok.\n\n
9.	Season with ground black pepper and then add fried tofu. Stir and cook for 2 minutes.\n\n
10.	Transfer to a serving bowl. Serve.\n\n
11.	Share and enjoy!
    </string>

    <string name="c21">
•	3 lbs. pork pata sliced\n
•	1 piece Knorr Pork Cube\n
•	3 pieces star anise\n\n
•	3 tablespoons brown sugar\n
•	1/4 cup soy sauce\n
•	1 piece onion chopped\n
•	4 cloves garlic crushed\n
•	1 tablespoon cornstarch\n
•	6 cups water\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking oil\n
•	Salt and ground white pepper to taste
    </string>

    <string name="c22">
1.	Prepare the pata by boiling. Pour water in a pot. Arrange pata slices. Cover and let boil. Continue boiling for 15 minutes while scraping scums and impurities. Discard water afterwards and wash the pork pata once it cools down. Set aside.\n\n
2.	Start cooking Sweet Pata Asado by heating oil in a pan. Sauté onion and garlic until onion softens.\n\n
3.	Add pata slices. Sautee for 1 minute.\n\n
4.	Pour soy sauce and water into the pot. Add star anise. Let boil.\n\n
5.	Add Knorr Pork Cube. Stir and cover. Set the heat between low and medium. Continue boiling until pata tenderizes. Note: make sure to stir once in a while to cook the meat evenly. Note: add more water as needed.\n\n
6.	Add sugar. Stir and cook for 3 minutes.\n\n
7.	Season with ground white pepper and salt.\n\n
8.	Combine cornstarch with 3 tablespoons water. Mix well. Pour mixture into the pot. Stir and cook until sauce thickens.\n\n
9.	Transfer to a serving bowl. Serve. Share and enjoy!\n\n

    </string>

    <string name="c23">
•	2 lbs spare ribs cut into serving pieces\n
•	20 oz. pineapple chunks in can\n
•	2 cups beef broth\n
•	1 piece onion\n
•	5 cloves garlic crushed\n
•	3 tablespoons soy sauce\n
•	2 1/2 tablespoons brown sugar\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking oil\n
•	Salt and ground black pepper to taste\n
    </string>

    <string name="c24">
1.	Separate pineapple juice from the chunks. Combine juice with spare ribs in a bowl. Marinate for at least 1 hour. Remove the juice afterwards and set aside.\n\n
2.	Heat oil in a pan. Saute onion and garlic until onion softens.\n\n
3.	Add marinated ribs. Saute until color turns light brown.\n\n
4.	Pour-in pineapple juice. Add soy sauce and beef broth. Stir. Let the mixture boil.\n\n
5.	Put the pineapple chunks into the pan. Cover and adjust the heat between low to medium. Cook for 1 hour.\n\n
6.	Add brown sugar and season with ground black pepper and salt. Continue cooking until sauce reduces to half.\n\n
7.	Transfer to a serving bowl. Serve with rice. Share and enjoy!
    </string>

    <string name="c25">
 •	2 1/2 lbs pork belly cubed\n
•	10 tablespoons white vinegar\n
•	3 tablespoons soy sauce\n
•	5 cloves garlic crushed\n
•	12 ounces cola drink\n
•	2 teaspoons whole peppercorn\n
•	4 pieces dried bay leaves\n
•	Salt optional\n
•	Water as needed
    </string>

    <string name="c26">
1.	Heat pan. Sear pork belly until it browns and enough oil is extracted. Note: stir the pork continuosly while searing.\n\n
2.	Push the pork on one side of the pan. Add garlic on the open area. Saute garlic for 30 seconds. Mix pork and garlic together. Cook for 1 minute.\n\n
3.	Pour-in soy sauce and vinegar. Let boil. Stir. Cook for 2 minutes.\n\n
4.	Add whole peppercorn and dry bay leaves.\n\n
5.	Add cola drink. Let it boil. Cover the pan. Continue cooking in low heat until pork gets tender. Note: add water if needed.\n\n
6.	Season with salt (optional).\n\n
7.	Transfer to a serving bowl. Serve. Share and enjoy!

    </string>

    <string name="c27">
•	2 lbs. pork belly cubed\n
•	7 tablespoons soy sauce\n
•	4 tablespoons white vinegar\n
•	1 can Sprite or similar soda pop\n
•	1 piece onion minced\n
•	5 pieces dried bay leaves\n
•	1 ½ teaspoons whole peppercorn\n
•	5 cloves garlic crushed\n
•	½ cup water\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking oil
    </string>

    <string name="c28">
1.	In a large bowl, combine soy sauce and Sprite with the pork belly. Mix well. Cover the bowl and refrigerate. Let the pork marinate for at least 6 hours.\n\n
2.	Using a kitchen sieve, drain the marinade out of the bowl. Set it aside.\n\n
3.	Heat oil in a cooking pot\n\n
4.	Once the oil becomes hot, saute garlic until light brown\n\n
5.	Add onion. Continue to saute until soft\n\n
6.	Add pork belly. Stir and cook until light brown\n\n
7.	Pour the marinade (Sprite and soy sauce). Cover the pot and let boil.\n\n
8.	Add whole peppercorn and dried bay leaves. Cover the pot and continue to cook for 30 minutes in medium heat.\n\n
9.	Pour vinegar into the pot. Let the liquid re-boil. Stir. Cover and cook for 25 to 30 minutes. Note: add water if needed.\n\n
10.	Transfer to a serving plate. Serve with rice.\n\n
11.	Share and enjoy!
    </string>

    <string name="c29">
•	1 ½ lbs. pork belly sliced\n
•	½ cup cornstarch\n
•	3 tablespoons fish sauce\n
•	¾ cup cooking oil\n\n
        <i>Sinigang Rice</i>\n
•	22 g Knorr Sinigang sa Sampaloc original mix\n
•	1 ½ cups rice\n
•	8 pieces long green beans chopped\n
•	1 piece onion diced\n
•	1 piece long green pepper sliced\n
•	3 cups water\n
•	Ground black pepper\n
•	½ teaspoon paprika\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking oil\n\n
        <i>Vegetable Tempura</i>\n
•	1 piece tomato sliced\n
•	6 pieces okra\n
•	1 piece eggplant sliced\n
•	1 ½ cups spinach\n
•	1 cup cake flour\n
•	1 piece egg yolk\n
•	1 cup cold water\n
•	¼ cup ice cubes\n
•	2 cups cooking oil

    </string>

    <string name="c30">
1.	Prepare the sinigang broth by boiling water in a cooking pot. Add pork belly. Cover the pot and continue boiling using low to medium heat for 30 minutes. Note: add more water as needed.\n\n
2.	Add Knorr Sinigang sa sampaloc (original mix). Stir. Cover the pot and continue boiling in medium heat for 15 minutes. Remove the pork from the pot and let it cool down.\n\n
3.	Start to cook the sinigang rice by washing the rice. Drain water. Pour sinigang broth into the rice cooker while filtering using a kitchen sieve. Cook until done. Note: you can use a rice cooker, or do the traditional way of cooking rice.\n\n
4.	While the rice is cooking, prep the pork by placing it in a resealable bag. Add fish sauce. Marinate for 15 minutes. Heat oil in a pan and then dredge the pork in cornstarch. Fry each side until it turns golden brown and crispy. Place in a plate lined with paper towel. Set aside.\n\n
5.	Time to stir-fry the rice. Heat oil in a pan. Add onion and cook for 30 seconds. Put the chopped long green beans and continue cooking for 1 ½ minutes. Add sliced long green pepper and cooked rice. Stir-fry for 1 to 2 minutes. Finish by seasoning with ground black pepper and paprika. Set aside.\n\n
6.	Make the vegetable tempura by heating oil to 360F. Combine the batter ingredients starting from the egg yolk and water. Mix well. Add ice cubes and then put-in the cake flour. Mix by holding 4 pieces of chopsticks and mix using a stabbing motion for 30 to 35 seconds. Note: the mixture should be lumpy, not smooth.\n\n
7.	Dredge the vegetables in cake flour and then dip in the batter. Fry each side for 2 to 3 minutes. Note: the spinach should only be fried for not more than 1 minute.\n\n
8.	Arrange the sinigang rice on a serving plate. Top with crispy liempo and serve with vegetable tempura.Share and enjoy!

    </string>

    <string name="c31">
•	2 lbs. pork cubed\n
•	1 piece Knorr Pork Cube\n
•	1 piece potato cubed\n
•	1 piece carrot cubed\n
•	3/4 cup green peas\n
•	1 piece red bell pepper\n
•	8 ounces tomato sauce\n
•	2 cups coconut milk\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking oil\n
•	Salt and ground black pepper to taste
    </string>

    <string name="c32">
1.	Heat oil in a pan. Add onion. Cook for 20 seconds. Put the garlic in the pan. Saute until onion becomes tender.\n\n
2.	Add pork. Saute until the pork turns light brown.\n\n
3.	Pour tomato sauce and stir. Add coconut milk. Stir and let boil.\n\n
4.	Add Knorr Pork Cube. Stir. Cover the pan and continue cooking between low to medium heat for 45 minutes to 1 hour, or until tender. Note: you can add more water as needed.\n\n
5.	Put the potato and carrot into the pan. Cover and cook using medium heat for 8 minutes.\n\n
6.	Add red bell pepper and green peas. Cook for 3 minutes.\n\n
7.	Season with ground black pepper and salt.\n\n
8.	Transfer to a serving plate. Serve and enjoy!
    </string>

    <string name="f1">
•	4 lbs beef neck bone chopped\n
•	1 piece Knorr Beef Cube\n
•	1 1/2 tablespoons soy sauce\n
•	2 cups water\n
•	1 piece green bell pepper sliced\n
•	1 piece red bell pepper sliced\n
•	1 piece potato cubed\n
•	1 piece carrots sliced\n
•	8 ounces tomato sauce\n
•	3 tablespoons peanut butter\n
•	1 tablespoon liver spread\n
•	5 pieces Thai chili pepper chopped\n
•	1 piece onion chopped\n
•	5 cloves garlic crushed\n
•	Salt and ground black pepper to taste\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking oil
    </string>

    <string name="f11">
1.	Heat oil in a cooking pot. Saute onion and garlic until onion softens\n\n
2.	Add beef. Saute until the outer part turns light brown.\n\n
3.	Add soy sauce. Pour tomato sauce and water. Let boil.\n\n
4.	Add Knorr Beef Cube. Cover the pressure cooker. Cook for 30 minutes.\n\n
5.	Pan-fry carrot and potato until it browns. Set aside.\n\n
6.	Add chili pepper, liver spread and peanut butter. Stir.\n\n
7.	Add bell peppers, fried potato and carrot. Cover the pot. Continue cooking for 5 to 7 minutes.\n\n
8.	Season with salt and ground black pepper. Serve.
    </string>

    <string name="f2">
•	1 lb. beef tenderloin thinly sliced\n
•	3 tablespoons oyster sauce\n
•	1 teaspoon soy sauce\n
•	1 ½ tablespoons cornstarch\n
•	1/2 teaspoon ground black pepper\n
•	1- piece green bell pepper sliced into thick strips\n
•	1- piece red bell pepper sliced into thick strips\n
•	1/2 cup cooking oil
    </string>

    <string name="f22">
1.	Combine beef, oyster sauce, soy sauce, and ground black pepper. Mix well. Let it stand for 5 minutes.\n\n
2.	Add cornstarch into the bowl. Mix until all ingredients are well distributed. Set aside.\n\n
3.	Heat oil in a pan. Fry bell peppers for 1 minute. Stir once in a while. Remove bell peppers from the pan. Set aside.\n\n
4.	Using the remaining oil, stir fry marinated beef until it starts to brown.\n\n
5.	Add fried bell peppers and toss until all ingredients are distributed.\n\n
6.	Transfer beef stir fry to a serving plate.\n\n
7.	Serve with rice. Share and Enjoy!
    </string>

    <string name="f3">
•	4 lbs. beef neck bone\n
•	1 piece Knorr beef cube\n
•	6 cups water\n
•	6 pieces tomato cubed\n
•	1 piece onion cubed\n
•	5 cloves garlic chopped\n
•	12 pieces sitaw sliced in 2-inch pieces\n
•	3 cups sweet potato leaves\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking oil\n
•	Patis and ground black pepper to taste
    </string>

    <string name="f33">
1.	Pour water in a cooking pot. Add beef. Let boil. Continue boiling for 60 to 890 minutes or until the meat tenderizes.\n\n
2.	Remove the beef from the pot. Set aside.\n\n
3.	Heat oil in a pan. Saute onion and garlic. Add tomato. Cook until onion and tomato softens.\n\n
4.	Put the beef neck bones into the pot. Saute for 2 minutes.\n\n
5.	Pour-in beef stock (water used to tenderize beef). Let boil.\n\n
6.	Add Knorr Beef Cube. Stir. Cook for 2 minutes.\n\n
7.	Season with patis and ground black pepper.\n\n
8.	Add sitaw. Cook for 5 minutes.\n\n
9.	Add sweet potato leaves (dahon ng kamote). Cover and cook for 2 minutes.\n\n
10.	Transfer to a serving bowl. Serve hot with rice.
    </string>

    <string name="f4">
•	3 1/2 lbs. beef chuck\n
•	1 piece Knorr Beef Cube\n
•	8 ounces tomato sauce\n
•	3 cups water\n
•	6 tablespoons soy sauce\n
•	1 1/2 tablespoons white vinegar\n
•	2 teaspoons whole peppercorn crushed\n
•	4 pieces bay leaves dried\n
•	1/2 piece lemon\n
•	2 tablespoons tomato paste\n
•	3 tablespoons butter\n
•	1/2 cup cooking oil\n
•	1 piece onion chopped\n
•	4 cloves garlic chopped
    </string>

    <string name="f44">
1.	Combine beef, crushed peppercorn, soy sauce, vinegar, dried bay leaves, lemon, and tomato sauce. Mix well. Marinate beef or at least 30 minutes.\n\n
2.	Put the marinated beef in a cooking pot along with remaining marinade. Add water. Let boil.\n\n
3.	Add Knorr Beef Cube. Stir. Cover the pot and cook for 40 minutes in low heat.\n\n
4.	Turn the beef over. Add tomato paste. Continue cooking until beef tenderizes. Set aside.\n\n
5.	Heat oil in pan. Fry the potato until it browns. Turn over and continue frying the opposite side. Remove from the pan and place on a clean plate. Do the same with the carrots.\n\n
6.	Save 3 tablespoons of cooking oil from the pan where the potato was fried. Saute onion and garlic until onion softens.\n\n
7.	Pour-in the sauce from the beef stew. Let boil. Add the beef. Cook for 2 minutes.\n\n
8.	Add butter and let it melt. Continue cooking until the sauce reduces to half.\n\n
9.	Remove the beef from the pan. Slice into serving pieces. Arrange on a serving plate with fried potato and carrot. Top with remaining sauce.\n\n
10.	Serve warm with rice. Share and enjoy!
    </string>

    <string name="f5">
•	1 lb ground beef\n
•	18 ounces tortilla chips\n\
•	1 teaspoon cumin\n
•	2 teaspoons chili powder\n
•	1 teaspoon garlic powder\n
•	1 teaspoon onion powder\n
•	Salt and pepper to taste\n
•	1 piece tomato chopped\n
•	1 piece Serrano pepper sliced\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking oil\n\n
        <i>Cheese Sauce:</i>\n
•	3 tablespoons butter\n
•	3 tablespoons all-purpose flour\n
•	2 cups fresh milk\n
•	8 ounces quick melt cheese\n
    </string>

    <string name="f55">
1.	Prepare the beef by heating oil in a pan. Add beef. Cook until it turns brown while constantly stirring. Add chili powder, cumin, garlic powder, onion powder, salt, and pepper. Stir until blended. Continue cooking for 2 minutes. Set aside.\n\n
2.	Make the cheese sauce by melting butter in a cooking pot. Add flour. Continuously stir for 3 minutes. Pour-in milk. Stir until the mixture smoothens. Add cheese. Cook while stirring until the cheese melts and the mixture becomes smooth.\n\n
3.	Assemble the beef nachos by placing the tortilla chips on a serving plate. Top with beef and cheese sauce.\n\n
4.	Add chopped tomato and some sliced Jalapeno or Serrano pepper on top. Serve. Share and enjoy!
    </string>

    <string name="f6">
•	1 lb beef heart cubed\n
•	1 lb beef small intestine cleaned\n
•	1 lb beef tripe cleaned\n
•	1/2 lb beef liver cubed\n
•	1 lb beef kidney cubed\n
•	22 grams Knorr Sinigang sa Sampaloc Mix\n
•	1 piece onion chopped\n
•	3 thumbs ginger minced\n
•	5 cloves garlic crushed\n
•	3 piece long green pepper sliced\n
•	8 cups water\n
•	beef bile to taste\n
•	Salt and pepper to taste\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking oil
    </string>

    <string name="f66">
1.	Wash beef tripe and small intestine. Boil with ginger and dried bay leaves for 45 minutes. Remove from the pot and let it cool down. Slice into bite-size pieces.\n\n
2.	Heat oil in a pan. Sauté onion, garlic, and ginger until onion softens.\n\n
3.	Add beef heart and kidney. Sauté until it turns light brown.\n\n
4.	Put the tripe and small intestines into the pot. Cook for 2 minutes.\n\n
5.	Pour water into the pot. Let is boil. Adjust heat to low. Continue boiling until beef heart and kidney tenderizes.\n\n
6.	Add beef liver and bile. Stir. Cook for 15 minutes in medium heat.\n\n
7.	Add Knorr Sinigang sa Sampaloc Recipe Mix.\n\n
8.	Put long green peppers into the pot and season with salt and ground black pepper. Stir. Cook for 2 minutes.\n\n
9.	Transfer to a serving bowl. Serve hot.
    </string>

    <string name="f7">
•	3 lbs beef shank bulalo\n
•	1 piece Knorr Beef Cube\n
•	1 cup roasted peanuts\n
•	15 pieces sitaw cut in 2-inch pieces\n
•	1 piece eggplant sliced\n
•	1 bunch bok choy\n
•	1/2 cup annatto seeds\n
•	8 cloves garlic crushed and chopped\n
•	1 1/2 pints water\n
•	2 teaspoons cornstarch diluted in 1/4 cup water\n
•	1/2 cup bagoong alamang\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking oil
    </string>

    <string name="f77">
1.	Heat oil in a pan. Saute onion and garlic until onion softens.\n\n
2.	Add beef shank. Cook each side for 30 seconds.\n\n
3.	Pour water into the pot. Let boil. Continue boiling for 10 minutes. Skim the scums on the surface. Continue boiling in low heat until meat gets tender.\n\n
4.	Prepare the annatto water by boiling 1 cup water in a saucepan. Add annatto seeds. Boil for 1 minute. Set aside.\n\n
5.	Prepare the peanut paste by placing the roasted peanuts in a food processor. Puree until the texture becomes smooth and paste-like.\n\n
6.	Once the beef shank tenderizes, add peanut paste and annatto water (filter the seeds using a kitchen strainer). Cover and cook for 5 minutes.\n\n
7.	Add Knorr Beef Cube. Stir. Cover and cook for 3 minutes.\n\n
8.	Pour cornstarch mixture. Stir until sauce thickens. Season with ground black pepper.\n\n
9.	Add eggplant and sitaw. Cover and cook for 5 minutes.\n\n
10.	Add bok choy. Cover and cook for 3 minutes. Transfer to a serving plate. Serve with bagoong alamang. Share and Enjoy!

    </string>

    <string name="f8">
•	12 ounces canned corned beef\n
•	1 piece Knorr Beef Cube\n
•	12 ounces fresh noodles\n
•	1 piece carrot minced\n
•	2 pieces eggs raw\n
•	½ cup all-purpose flour\n
•	5 tablespoons cornstarch\n
•	1 piece onion chopped\n
•	4 cloves garlic crushed\n
•	½ cup green onion chopped\n
•	2 tablespoons soy sauce\n
•	2 pieces eggs boiled\n
•	1 cup chicharon\n
•	6 cups water\n
•	½ cup cooking oil\n
•	Salt and ground black pepper to taste
    </string>

    <string name="f88">
1.	Make the meatballs by combining ¾ the amount of the corned beef, carrot, salt, ground black pepper, and 1-piece cracked egg in a bowl. Mix well. Gradually add all-purpose flour and continue mixing until all ingredients are well blended.\n\n
2.	Heat oil in pan. Scoop 1 ½ tablespoon of mixture and mold into a ball-shaped figure. Fry in low heat for 1 ½ minutes per side. Remove from the pan and transfer to a clean plate. Set aside.\n\n
3.	Transfer the remaining oil on a pot. Heat and then sauté garlic until it starts to brown. Add onion and continue cooking until the later softens.\n\n
4.	Add remaining corned beef from the can. Sauté for 1 minute.\n\n
5.	Pour water into pot. Let boil.\n\n
6.	Add Knorr Beef Cube. Stir. Pour-in soy sauce and add fresh noodles. Cover and cook for 5 minutes.\n\n
7.	Combine cornstarch and ½ cup water. Mix well. Pour the mixture into the pot. Stir until the soup thickens.\n\n
8.	Crack a piece of egg into the pot. Quickly stir and continue cooking for 1 minute.\n\n
9.	Add fried meatballs and season with salt and ground black pepper. Cook for 3 minutes.\n\n
10.	Transfer to a serving bowl. Top with meatballs, boiled egg, chicharron, and chopped green onions.\n\n
11.	Serve warm. Share and enjoy!

    </string>

    <string name="f9">
•	1 ½ lbs. beef sirloin\n
•	3 tablespoons soy sauce\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking wine\n
•	4 tablespoons oyster sauce\n
•	2 tablespoons cornstarch\n
•	2 cups broccoli florets\n
•	2 thumbs ginger\n
•	1 piece onion\n
•	1 ½ cup beef broth\n
•	3 tablespoons cooking oil\n
•	Salt and pepper to taste
    </string>

    <string name="f99">
1.	Combine beef, soy sauce, cooking wine, and cornstarch in a bowl. Mix well. Marinate for 15 minutes.\n\n
2.	Heat oil in a pan. Sauté ginger and onion until the later softens.\n\n
3.	Add marinated beef into the pan. Stir-fry until the beef browns.\n\n
4.	Add oyster sauce. Stir-fry for 1 minute.\n\n
5.	Pour-in beef broth. Stir. Cover the pan and then continue cooking in low heat for 10 to 12 minutes.\n\n
6.	Add broccoli. Stir and cover the pan. Cook for 3 minutes.\n\n
7.	Season with salt and ground black pepper.\n\n
8.	Transfer to a serving plate. Serve! Share and enjoy.
    </string>

    <string name="f10">
•	3/4 lbs beef sirloin sliced into thin strips\n\
•	15 pieces baby corn\n
•	1 1/2 cups snap peas\n
•	1 small red bell pepper sliced into strips\n
•	1/4 cup light soy sauce\n
•	3 to 4 tablespoons oyster sauce\n
•	1 1/2 tablespoons cornstarch\n
•	1/2 teaspoon ground black pepper\n
•	1/2 teaspoon salt\n
•	3 table spoon Shoaxing cooking wine\n
•	3 tablespoon cooking oil
    </string>

    <string name="f1010">
1.	Arrange beef in a bowl. Add 1/4 teaspoon ground black pepper, soy sauce, and oyster sauce. Mix well.\n\n
2.	Add the cornstarch. Make sure all the ingredients are well blended. Set aside.\n\n
3.	Meanwhile, heat a wok or a pan. Pour-in the cooking oil. Once the oil gets hot, stir-fry the baby corn, snap peas, and red bell pepper for 3 to 5 minutes.\n\n
4.	Add salt and remaining pepper. Pour the cooking wine in the wok and stir-fry for 3 minutes.\n\n
5.	Transfer the vegetables to a plate. Set aside.\n\n
6.	Using the remaining cooking oil (add a tablespoon of cooking oil if needed), stir fry the marinated beef for 3 to 4 minutes. Add the stir-fried vegetables and continue to stir-fry for another 2 to 4 minutes.\n\n
7.	Transfer to a serving plate. Serve.\n\n
8.	Share and enjoy!

    </string>

    <string name="recipe">
        Reference:\n
        https://www.allrecipes.com/recipes/ \n
        https://www.allrecipes.com/recipes/1947/everyday-cooking/quick-and-easy/ \n
        https://www.simplyrecipes.com/ \n\n
        Thank you!!
    </string>

</resources>